[
  {
    "front": "비/비가 오다",
    "back": "Rain"
  },
  {
    "front": "온종일",
    "back": "All day long"
  },
  {
    "front": "지루한",
    "back": "Fed up"
  },
  {
    "front": "밖으로",
    "back": "Outside"
  },
  {
    "front": "창문",
    "back": "Window"
  },
  {
    "front": "마법",
    "back": "Magic"
  },
  {
    "front": "모험",
    "back": "Adventure"
  },
  {
    "front": "보트",
    "back": "Boat"
  },
  {
    "front": "걱정하지 마",
    "back": "Don't worry"
  },
  {
    "front": "구하다",
    "back": "Save"
  },
  {
    "front": "동물",
    "back": "Animal"
  },
  {
    "front": "도와주다",
    "back": "Help"
  },
  {
    "front": "가리키다",
    "back": "Point"
  },
  {
    "front": "코끼리",
    "back": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "front": "밀다",
    "back": "Push"
  },
  {
    "front": "당기다",
    "back": "Pull"
  },
  {
    "front": "남기다/떠나다",
    "back": "Leave"
  },
  {
    "front": "아직도",
    "back": "Still"
  }
]